<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<event>
	<end>0</end>
	<end>1</end>
	<end>2</end>
	<end>3</end>
	<end>4</end>
	<end>5</end>
	<end>6</end>
	<end>7</end>
	<end>8</end>
	<end>9</end>
	<end>10</end>
	<end>11</end>
	<end>12</end>
	<end>13</end>
	<end>14</end>
	<end>15</end>
	<end>16</end>
	<end>17</end>
	<end>18</end>
	<dialog id="0">
		<eventText>
			You throw the tank top over your head but you have trouble finding the holes for your arms. The top fits on you like a tent, clearly several sizes too large for your frame.
			You take the tanktop off, dissatisfied with its extremely loose fit.
			Holding the blue jeans against your waist, you can immediately tell they're too large as well.
			Tough luck.
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="1">
		<eventText>
			You throw the tank top over your head and slide your arms through the holes. It's a super loose fit on your frame.
			Holding the blue jeans to your waist, you can tell they will also be too large. However, you try them on anyways.
			They sag below your waist, on the verge of falling off.
			Lose any more weight and they surely will.
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="2">
		<eventText>
			You throw the tank top over your head and slide your arms through the holes. It's a loose fit, but it's manageable.
			The jeans are next. You pull them up to your waist and have no problems buttoning them up.
			They slide a little bit down your waist, possibly a bit too large.
			Gain a little bit more weight and these will fit perfectly.
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="3">
		<eventText>
			You throw the tank top over your head and slide your arms through the holes easily. It fits perfect on your frame.
			The jeans are next. You pull them up to your waist and have no problems buttoning them up.
			The jeans are also a perfect fit.
			It's your lucky day!
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="4">
		<eventText>
			You throw the tank top over your head and slide your arms through the holes. It's a bit of a tight fit on your frame.
			The jeans are next. You pull them up to your waist and manage to button them up.
			They're a bit snug around your hips, but still a decent fit.
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="5">
		<eventText>
			You throw the tank top over your head and struggle to slide your arms through the holes.
			After a bit of difficulty, you can pull down the tank top to your waist. It exposes a bit of your belly, clearly a few sizes too small.
			The jeans are next. You pull them up to your waist and struggle to button them.
			Eventually you get it, however they're very tight around your waist.
			Sigh... you may need to consider a diet.
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="6">
		<eventText>
			You throw the tank top over your head and can barely fit your thick arms through the holes.
			After a long struggle, you finally pull down the tank top to your waist. It slides back up to your bra-line, clearly several sizes too small.
			The jeans are next. You can hardly pull them up to your waist, but you eventually manage.
			Miraculously, you're able to button them, but it may not be long before they pop.
			Should you gain any more weight, the future of these jeans will be grim.
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="7">
		<eventText>
			You throw the tank top over your head and can hardly fit your chubby arms through the holes.
			After a long struggle, you finally pull down the tank top to your waist but it immediately rides back up to your bra-line, clearly several sizes too small.
			The jeans are next. The seams groan as you pull them up to your waist.
			Your fat ass is pressed hard against the fabrics of the jeans.
			You manage to zip the jeans halfway up, but it will be near-impossible to button them.
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="8">
		<eventText>
			You throw the tank top over your head, but after a struggling for a bit, you find that your flabby arms cannot fit through the holes.
			After fighting to pull the jeans beyond your thunder thighs, you hit an insurmountable obstacle - your fat ass.
			It becomes clear that your ass is just too damn big to fit into the jeans.
			Seeing as you're already bursting at the seams, and the jeans aren't fully up yet, it might be best to admit defeat.
			Sigh... nothing fits anymore...
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="9">
		<eventText>
			You throw the tank top over your head but immediately discover that your chunky arms are way too big to fit through the holes.
			You don't want to tear the shirt, so you decide to not go any further.
			It's laughable that you even thought the jeans would fit. Holding them to your waist, they're clearly designed for somebody half your size.
			It's almost comical how small they look compared to your massive thunder thighs and bountiful hips.
			God... how depressing...
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="10">
		<eventText>
			Your jeans have fallen right off. Your tank top fits like a tent on your frame. It'll be impossible to wear these unless you gain a considerable amount of weight.
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="11">
		<eventText>
			Your jeans are becoming extremely loose around your waist. They sag down, showing your panties.
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="12">
		<eventText>
			Your jeans are now loose around your waist.
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="13">
		<eventText>
			Your jeans and tank top now fit perfectly on your frame.
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="14">
		<eventText>
			Your jeans are now snug around your waist. Your tank top is a bit snug around your belly.
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="15">
		<eventText>
			Your jeans are now tight around your waist. Your tank top rides up, exposing a bit of your lower stomach.
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="16">
		<eventText>
			Your jeans are now uncomfortably tight around your waist. Your tank top rides up, exposing your deep naval.
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="17">
		<eventText>
			Your jeans begin to creak and groan at the seams. Gain any more weight and they will burst. Your tank top rides up to your bra-line, completely exposing your bare belly. The sleeves are tight around your flabby arms.
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="18">
		<eventText>
			The button on your jeans bursts open, and they unzip. The fabrics erupt in resounding groans and tears. You glance behind you to find a massive hole in your jeans, exposing your butt. These jeans have had it. Your tank top is also a goner, as you notice the sleeves are ripped due to battling with your immense arm fat. Sigh... you need to find a tailor to fix these clothes, otherwise they are unwearable.
		</eventText>
	</dialog>
</event>