<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<event>
	<end>5</end>
	<precondition>CurrentFloorID=1</precondition>
	<dialog id='0'>
		<eventText>An androgynous looking fairy enters your field of vision. Talk to it? </eventText>
		<option id='1'>Yes</option>
		<option id='5'>No</option>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id='1'>
		<eventText>"I can make you gain or lose weight. Take your pick," it squeaks.</eventText>
		<option id='2' action="Weight+50">Gain</option>
		<option id='3' action="Weight*0.8">Lose</option>
		<option id='4'>No thanks</option>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id='2'>
		<eventText precondition="BMI&gt;34">The fairy shakes its head in disapproval. "I don't know why you'd want to be fatter than you already are, but here goes." </eventText>
		<eventText>The fairy waves its arms to produce a bright flash of light, enough to blind you temporarily. </eventText>
		<eventText precondition="Belly&lt;19">When your vision returns, you stare down at your now-curvy midsection. You used to be able to see your abs, but not anymore. </eventText>
		<eventText precondition="Belly&gt;19&amp;Belly&lt;25">When your vision returns, you stare down at your chubby tummy. A roll of fat slightly hangs over your waistband. </eventText>
		<eventText precondition="Belly&gt;34&amp;Belly&lt;45">When your vision returns, you stare down at your bulging belly and marvel at its size. It extends so far that you cannot see your feet without bending over. </eventText>
		<eventText precondition="Belly&gt;24&amp;Belly&lt;35">When your vision returns, you stare down at your pudgy belly. It hangs over your waistband. </eventText>
		<eventText precondition="Belly&gt;44">When your vision returns, you peek down at your sagging gut. It hangs to your knees and blocks a good portion of the ground in front of you from your field of vision. </eventText>
		<eventText>True to its word, the fairy made you fatter!</eventText>
		<option id='5'>Continue</option>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id='3'>
		<eventText>The fairy waves its arms to produce a bright flash of light, enough to blind you temporarily. When your vision returns, you stare down at your stomach, much flatter than it was previous. True to its word, the fairy made you thinner.
		</eventText>
		<option id='5'>Continue</option>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id='4'>
		<eventText>"Okay. Suit yourself."</eventText>
		<option id='5'>Continue</option>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id='5'>
		<eventText>The fairy disappears in a shimmer of light.</eventText>
	</dialog>
</event>